fontsquirrel.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Font Squirrel

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

**Information You Provide.** We receive and store information you enter. For example, when you search for or buy a product or service, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you. In addition, if you opt-in, we may share your information with other companies who provide goods or services that you are interested in. 

**Cookies.** Like many websites, we use "cookies". Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser, and clicking on the “help” button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie. In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies. 

**Other Information:** Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site.

**Information from Other Sources.** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. This may include updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

### How Do We Use Your Information?

**Customized Shopping.** We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized shopping experience. As noted above, you may “opt-out” of this customization, or even visit and shop anonymously.

**Agents.** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Special Offers.** We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to “opt-out” of receiving such offers. In addition, we may also send you special offers from other companies. Again, you may “opt-out”.

**Advertising.** We use your data for advertising purposes. We use third-party advertising companies who serve ads to help keep content free. For these partners, we put additional restrictions on how your data can be used to prevent it from misuse. For instance, we do not allow these partners to take your information for profiling and personalizing ads on other sites. Please review the following for a full list of partners and purposes: [PubGalaxy (Titan Gate AD)](https://www.pubgalaxy.com/privacy-policy.html). 

### How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list.

We limit access to your information on a “need to know” basis.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

No system can guarantee absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical security. However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure.

### Children

We do not knowingly sell products or services to children. If you are under 13, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

### Other Websites

Various Web sites may be linked to from this site. If you link to another site, your privacy depends on the policy of that site. We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy. Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others. You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance (www.privacyalliance.org).

### Contact Us

If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, or to access your personally identifiable information contained on our website, you may contact us at [ethan@fonthead.com](mailto:ethan@fonthead.com). You will be required to provide identifier information to assure that this information is not released to others. We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future.
